https://www.toolsource.com/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
This is the Web site of ToolSource.com.
Our postal address is:
ToolSource™
ATTN: Customer Service Dept.
6277 Sugartown RD
P.O. Box 950
Ellicottville, NY 14731
We can be reached via e-mail at Service@ToolSource.com. You can also reach us by telephone at 1-888-220-8350, or fax at 716-699-8337.
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for ToolSource.com. This statement covers the following areas:
Notification of Changes
If you feel that ToolSource.com is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact ToolSource.com by any of the above methods.
Information Collection and Use
ToolSource.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. ToolSource.com collects information from our users at several different points on our website.
Order & Registration
We request information from the user on our registration and order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.
Cookies
In addition, like most other e-commerce Websites, our site uses "cookies," or our unique electronic fingerprint placed temporarily in your Internet browser, to keep track of your stay at our Website. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. The cookie allows our server to remember you and the items you've placed in your shopping cart and therefore enables us to customize our site to your needs. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. The cookie is harmless and does not gather information from your computer or profile your system. It simply allows us to distinguish each individual among the many shoppers that browse our site and expires a specific period of time after your visit.
Mailings, E-Mail & Newsletters
If you supply us with your email address, your postal address or telephone number online you may receive periodic mailings, e-mails or telephone calls from us with information that may be of interest to you regarding new products, services or upcoming specials. If you do not wish to receive e-mails from us, please let us know by sending an email to Remove@ToolSource.com. Include the e-mail address you wish to be removed in separate line in the body of the e-mail. You may also submit your request via mail at the address listed at the top of this page. We will promptly remove your addresses and telephone numbers from our lists.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Sharing of Information
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers (example: 46% of our users identify themselves as Technicians, while 50% identify themselves as Shop Owners, etc.). This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this web site.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off line.
When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. To learn more about SSL, follow this link Security Information.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information off line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers? information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.
If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to Service@ToolSource.com.
Correction/Updating Personal Information
If a user?s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done at the account information page, or by e-mail to Service@- ToolSource.com or by sending us a letter at our postal address set forth at the beginning of this policy.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If a user wishes us to remove that user's personal data provided to us as the result of such change, this can be done at the account information page or by email to Service@ToolSource.com or by sending us a letter at our postal address set forth at the beginning of this policy.
Back
Facebook
Twitter
google +
Mail
youtube
Manufacturers
Please Select
10C Technologies
2 x 4 Basics
303 Products
3M Automotive
4 Sight
9 Circle
Absolute Coatings (POR15)
Access Tools
Accumetric
AccuSharp
AccuTorq
ACDelco
Acme Automotive
Actron Manufacturing
Advance Design Systems
AOK Industrial Company
Apache Hose & Belting Co.
Apex Tool Group
Armstrong
Arrow Pneumatics
ASG Division - Jergens Inc
Assenmacher Specialty Tools
Associated Equipment
Astoria 2000
Astro Pneumatic
Crystal - Bond Corporation
CTA Manufacturing Corp.
CTEK Power Inc
CURIEN
Custom Auto Air
Custom Leathercraft
Cyclo Industries
Darex LLC
Dawson
Delphi
Induction Innovations
Industro, Inc.
Infratech
Infratech Automotive
Ingersoll-Rand
Ingersoll-Rand Compressors
Ingersoll-Rand Parts
Injectoclean
Innovative Products of America
INOVA
Inox
Insight Technology
Interdynamics
Intermarket (AFF Jax)
Intertape Polymer Group
INTERTEX
Irega
Irwin
ITW Global Brands
Iwata
J.H. Williams
Jack Tech
Merfin Hygienic
Merrick Machine Co.
Metabo
Mi-T-M
Mibro
Michigan Ind Tools
Micro Flex
Microfiber and More
MicroFlex
Midtronics
Mopar Essential Tools
Morgan Mfg Inc.
Mothers Wax & Polish
Motion Pro
Motor City Tools
Motor Guard
Motor Information Systems
MotorVac Technologies
Mountain
Mr. Heater
Prevost
Prime Supply Inc.
Primeline Tools Inc.
Private Brand Tools
Pro Maxx Engineered Products
Pro MotorCar Products Inc.
Pro-Tek
Professional Tool Products
Protecto Seal
ProtektoTrim Cowles Products
Protoco Enterprises Co
ProVision
Quick-Grip
Quip-All
R & D Kamas
R W THOMPSON INC
R-2 Manufacturing
R3 Safety
Racatac Inc.
Radiator Specialty Company
Rail Saver
RamRodz
Rapala
RapidFix
Ratch-Cut
Rayovac
Raytek
Reelcraft
REL Products, Inc.
Remwood
Rennsteig
Revo Brand Group LLC
Rhino Gear
Rhino Tools
Ridgid
Ringers Gloves
Roadi
Sarge
SAS Safety Corp.
Sata Spray Equipment
Save Phace
SCA Tissue
Schlegel Corp
Schley Products, Inc
Schrade
Schrader-bridgeport Internationa
Schumacher Electric
Solar
Solder-It Inc.
Solv-Tec
Sondpex
SP Air Corporation
Specialty Products
Spectrum Composites
Sperian
Spray-X LLC
Sprayway Inc
Tiger Tool
Time Shaver Tools Inc.
Tire Service Equipment
Titan
Todd Enterprises
Tommyco
Tool Box Grill
Tool Cache
Tool Grid
ToolSource
UFO
Ullman Devices Corp.
Umarex USA Inc.
Uneeda Enterprises Inc.
Uni-Ram Corp.
Unibit
Unitec
United Cutlery
United Marketing
Universal Test Tools, Inc.
Universal Tool
Uniweld Products
Urethane Supply Company
Uriah Products
US Chemical & Plastics
Uvex
Uview
V8 Tools
Vacula Automotive Products
Vacutec
Vampire Tools
Vantage Tool
Vaughan & Bushnell Mfg.
Ventamatic Ltd.
Vermont American
Vessel Tools USA
Vibac
Victor - Firepower
Viking Air Tools
Viledon Air Filter
VIM Tools
Viper - Clore Automotive
Reconditioned
New Products ...
Featured Products ...
All Products ...
New Products
BOSCH OBD 1150• Compatible with ALL 1996 and newer import , domestic, diesel and h$130.403-JAW, 2-TON PULLER• Manual puller with three jaws for extraction of most shaft-fitted $118.67ACICULAR PROBE - BLACKAcicular Probe (Black), Qty 5$11.36
Reviews
Overall I'm extremely satisfied with tool source I selected the norma
Featured
Air/Hydraulic Truck Jack - 22-Ton CapacityChrome plated lift armSelf-retracting ram springs for fast ram retractionPush va$540.99Telescoping Transmission Jack - 1000 Lb CapacityHandles all passenger car, van, and light truck automotive transmissions, front $731.63
Information
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
Contact Us
Site Map
coupon code FAQ
Discount Coupons
